vmcsatellite.com 2010-06-26

# 

**Privacy Policy**

**Simply put, we promise that:**

·                     We will only ask for personal information required to complete your order. 

·                     We will use security safeguards such as SSL encryption to protect your information. 

·                     We will never use your personal information for the purpose of spam. 

|   
---|---  
  
**Protecting Your Privacy and Security**

·                     _TRUSTe Certified_

·                     What Information We Collect and How We Use It

    * _Non-Personally Identifiable Information_

      * Location Information
      * Cookies
      * Tracking Pixels
      * _Online Preference Marketing_

    * Personally Identifiable Information

      * _Order Information_
      * Forward-To-A-Friend and Refer-A-Friend
      * Supplementation of Information
      * _Affiliate Sign-Up Process_
      * Live Help and Chat Function
      * _Social Media_ __
      * _Surveys_ __

·                     Sharing of Your Information

    * _Trusted Third Parties_
    * _Co-branded Web sites and Offers_
    * _Links_
    * _Legal Process/Disclaimer_ __

·                     Security

·                     Reviewing and Making Choices About the Use of Your Information

    * _Reviewing and Updating Your Information_
    * _Choices/Opt Out_
    * Contact Us

·                     _Updates and Notification of Changes_ _to this Privacy Policy_

·                     _Acceptance of this Privacy Policy_

**TRUSTe Certified**

We value the relationship we have with our users and customers and are committed to responsible information-handling practices. We take great care in safeguarding your personal information and exceeding our own internal standards and best practices.

The [Partner Description] store is operated by Simplexity, LLC ("Simplexity"). We provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used by our site. This Privacy Policy covers the site www.VMCSatellite.com.

Simplexity is a participant in the TRUSTe Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to advance privacy and trust in the networked world.  Simplexity wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy so we have agreed to disclose our information practices and have our privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, Simplexity has agreed to notify you of: 

·                     What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Web site; 

·                     How the information is used; 

·                     With whom the information may be shared; 

·                     What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;

·                     What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Simplexity’s control; and 

·                     How you can correct or update your information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, or complaints arising from our use of your personal information, please contact us via certified mail at: Simplexity, LLC, c/o Privacy Administration, 10790 Parkridge Boulevard, Suite 200, Reston, VA 20191 or via e-mail at privacypolicy@simplexity.com. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry, or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you may contact TRUSTe through the TRUSTe WatchDog Dispute Resolution Process ([www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php)). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with Simplexity to resolve your concerns. 

**What Information We Collect and How We Use It**

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

_Location Information_

We collect location information in order to improve your shopping experience. If you shop for location-specific products such as a wireless or satellite rate plan, we ask for a zip code and record this information via a cookie so that we may display only services which are available in your area. We also save this information so that we don’t have to ask for it again on your next visit.

We also collect information about your computer, including without limitation hardware, software and configuration information, your IP address, operating system, browser type, domain name of your Internet service provider, URL, access times and/or referring Web site address. We use this information to evaluate and track your order, help administer our Web site, examine overall traffic trends and to help improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. We also use this information to improve the design and content of our Web site, personalize your Internet experience, analyze service usage, track user activity and minimize fraud.

_Cookies_

Cookies are used by your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or personally identifiable information. In addition, some of our advertisers and business affiliates may use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies and their use is not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

_Tracking Pixels_

This site makes use of a technology designed to enhance your browsing experience. The technology makes use of a small and transparent Java applet to provide you with a faster browsing experience. In addition, aggregate reporting information is collected and made available to the site owner only. No personal or personally identifiable information is gathered or used in this process.

_Online Preference Marketing_

We use third party advertising companies and advertising networks, including without limitation Microsoft and AudienceScience, to serve targeted behavioral and multi-site advertisements to you on our behalf when you visit our Web site.  They do this by researching and collecting Web site usage and behavioral data through the use of cookies, monitoring technologies and Web beacons to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you on our, and other, Web sites. These companies do not use your personally identifiable information to provide this service. If you would like more information about this practice, or to opt-out of the collection of this information on our Web site, please visit: _[http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp)_ ; and/or [http://privacy.microsoft.com](http://privacy.microsoft.com/).

**Personally Identifiable Information**

_Order Information_

When you place an order for products or services we collect certain types of personally identifiable information required to fulfill those product and/or service order, including (1) contact information (such as name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number); (2) payment information (such as credit card number); and/or (3) ID verification information (such as credit card number, date of birth, Social Security Number, and/or Driver's License Number).

We collect ID verification information to determine your eligibility and/or process your application We, and/or the service provider, may perform an identity and/or credit check as a part of our fraud protection and order fulfillment process. In the event that your order is not approved by the service provider of your choice without a deposit, we may also submit your data to an alternate service provider who also may perform an identity and/or credit check. 

If you would like to place an order but are reluctant to provide this information online, you may provide it to us by telephone during our normal business hours. For wireless products and services, telephone agents are available when the Order By Phone button is visible on one of the shopping pages of our site. Simply click on this button to speak to an agent and provide your information over the phone. For home connectivity services, telephone agents are available Monday through Friday, 9AM to 6PM. They can be reached at 1-800-998-3474 for satellite services and 1-800-401-0158 for security services.

We use the contact information you provide to communicate with you, such as to send you order confirmations, respond to your inquiries and provide you with important product updates, warranty and/or safety information. In addition, we use contact information you provide to offer you additional products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.  You can easily opt out of receiving marketing emails by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the e-mail.  Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes unless you authorize us to do so.

### _ _

### _Forward-To-A-Friend and Refer-A-Friend_

If you choose to use our email forwarding functionality or our referral service to tell a friend about our Web site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend the forwarded email or a one-time promotional email, as applicable. We use this information for the sole purpose of forwarding the email or sending the one-time promotional email and delete the information afterwards. 

_Supplementation of Information_

We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect online with outside records (e.g., information from our strategic partners, service providers, or the United States Postal Service) to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

_Affiliate Sign-Up Process_

If you register to be one of our Affiliates, the data you submit in the Affiliate Sign-Up Process may be collected by or submitted by us to a third-party company that we may designate to manage our Affiliates program(s).  In such cases, we will disclose the name of the third-party company and you will be subject to that third party’s privacy policy.

_Live Help and Chat Function_

To better serve you and promptly address your questions regarding our wireless and/or home connectivity products and/or services, we also maintain a Live Chat function through which we can respond in real time to your questions. Information collected through Live Chat sessions may be monitored or recorded by us or by our Live Chat platform provider.  This information allows us to complete or update your order, train employees and provide high-quality customer service.

_Social Media_

If you use a blog on one of our Web sites, any personally identifiable information you submit or post on such sites can be read, collected, and/or used by other users of these sites. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit on these sites. 

_Surveys_

During and/or after your visit to our Web site, we may ask you questions about our products and services and/or your shopping experience.  If you submit answers to these questions, we may place your answers and your first name on our Web site to inform other customers and improve their shopping experience, but we will not list any personally identifiable information other than your first name without first receiving your approval to do so. 

**Sharing of Your Information**

**Trusted Third Parties** ****

Please be assured that any third parties who have access to the information you provide, including our marketing partners, agents, contractors and business affiliates, have agreed to protect it in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. To fulfill your requests for products and services, we may need to share some of your personally identifiable information with the service provider from which you have requested service. More specifically, when you place an order, we will share contact and ID verification information required by the service provider. The service provider may use this information for credit approval, service activation, and from time to time, its own marketing purposes in accordance with its privacy policy. You should consult the service providers' privacy policy, as this Privacy Policy does not cover their use of your information. We may need to share your personally identifiable information with other third party service providers that assist us with online chat services, credit card processing, fraud screening and shipping in connection with your order and/or use of our site.  We also work closely with and may share your contact information with trusted third party business affiliates to provide you with information on products and services that may be of interest to you. 

**Co-branded Web Sites and Offers**

In addition, you can access Simplexity through many third party co-branded Web sites and partner marketing efforts. For example, if you see a logo on the page that says "Powered by Simplexity," you are on a co-branded page. Whenever you provide contact information on a co-branded page, that data may be shared with the third party site or partner through which you access Simplexity. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of such third parties, as their privacy policy also governs their use of your information.

Simplexity sometimes may offer content (e.g., promotions, affiliations, sponsorships) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable and other information that users voluntarily submit or authorize Simplexity to provide to accept the offer. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of such third parties, as their privacy policy also governs the maintenance and use of your information.

**Links**

This site may contain links to other Web sites whose information practices may be different from ours. Our Privacy Policy does not cover these third party Web sites’ uses of your information. Visitors should consult the sites' privacy notice as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

**Legal Process/Disclaimer**

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to or in connection with judicial or regulatory proceedings or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency's request.

**Security**

We have put in place multiple levels of physical and electronic security to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to our systems, maintain data security and securely use the information we collect. These measures include secure Web pages, VeriSign SSL certificate ensuring the privacy and security of order information, and HackerSafe certification, representing the highest security scanning standards of the U.S. government and all major credit card providers. All information submitted is protected by our secure server, which automatically encrypts your personally identifiable information so that it cannot be read while traveling over the Internet.

**Reviewing and Making Choices About the Use of Your Information**

**_Reviewing and Updating Your Information_**

If you would like to review, update and/or correct the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you online, simply send your request via certified mail to: Simplexity, LLC, c/o Privacy Administration, 10790 Parkridge Boulevard, Suite 200, Reston, VA 20191 or via e-mail to privacypolicy@simplexity.com. For wireless service customers, you may also send your request via the Customer Support feedback section in our [customer service center](http://www.whereismyorder.com/). To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your personal information. 

**_Choices/Opt Out_** __

If you prefer not to receive marketing information, including emails, from us, or wish to deactivate your account information if you are no longer an active customer, simply send your request via certified mail to: Simplexity, LLC, c/o Privacy Administration, 10790 Parkridge Boulevard, Suite 200, Reston, VA 20191 or via e-mail to privacypolicy@simplexity.com. Please note that if you choose to opt out of marketing programs, you will continue to receive important service-related communications (e.g., order confirmation or product safety information) which is not promotional in nature. 

**_Contact Us_**

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, or would like more information on our privacy practices, simply send your inquiry to us via certified mail at: Simplexity, LLC, c/o Privacy Administration, 10790 Parkridge Boulevard, Suite 200, Reston, VA 20191 or via e-mail to privacypolicy@simplexity.com.

**Updates and Notification of Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

**Acceptance of this Privacy Policy**

By visiting this Web site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**Last Updated February 2010**
